Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the Vice-President Records 1937-1946
University of Chicago Library
- Broadcasting, Chicago Title and Trust Co., 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Broadcasting, Columbia Broadcasting System, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Broadcasting, Columbia Broadcasting System, 1939-1940, Atlass, H. Leslie Coulter, Douglas Kesten, Paul Klauber, Edward Lagemann, John Lewerth, Margaret Morgan, Brewster Ratner, Victor Reed, Luther Sioussat, Helen Stanton, Frank Weber, Ted Wylie, Max (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Broadcasting, Columbia Broadcasting System, 1940-1941, Atlass, H. Leslie Coulter, Douglas Kane, James Klauber, Edward Reid, Joseph Schwartz, Lavinia Seldes, Gilbert Spier, William Stanton, Paul White, Paul Wylie, Max (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Broadcasting, Columbia Broadcasting System, 1941-1942, Atlass, H. Leslie Bryson, Lyman Costello, Mrs. William Coulter, Douglas Kesten, Paul Klauber, Edward (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Broadcasting, Columbia Broadcasting System, 1943-1944, Bryson, Lyman Burton, LaVerne Kesten, Paul (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Broadcasting, Columbia Broadcasting System, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Broadcasting, Columbia Broadcasting System, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Broadcasting, Cooperative Analysis of Broadcasting (CAB) ratings, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Broadcasting, Coronet, Round Table broadcast, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Broadcasting, Denny, George V., 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Broadcasting, Dos and Don'ts booklet, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., July-October, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., November-December, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., January-March, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., April-June, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., July-September, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., October, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., November, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., December, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., January-February, including chapter on Radio Broadcasting from The University of Chicago's Public Relations, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., March, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., April, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., May-June, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., July-September, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., October-November, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., "How to Listen to the Radio", 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., December-January, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., February-April, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., May-June, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., July-September, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., October-November, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., January-June, 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., July-November, 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., December-June, 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., copies of correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Broadcasting, Dryer, Sherman H., 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Broadcasting, Dupee, Gordon, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Broadcasting, Education for Freedom, Inc., 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Broadcasting, Faculty Advisory Committee on Radio, 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Broadcasting, Fadiman-Adler recording, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Broadcasting, Fisher, Sterling, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Broadcasting, Fisher, Sterling, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Broadcasting, Fisher, Sterling, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Broadcasting, Fisher, Sterling, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Broadcasting, General Education Board, 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Broadcasting, Haydon, Brownlee, 1939-1940 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Broadcasting, Haydon, Brownlee, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Broadcasting, Haydon, Brownlee, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Broadcasting, Haydon, Brownlee, 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Broadcasting, Hawk, Virginia, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Broadcasting, Hawk, Virginia, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Broadcasting, Hayek broadcast, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Broadcasting, Hooper Definitive Ratings, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Broadcasting, Hooper, general correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Broadcasting, Howe's Round Table material, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, presentation to the Board of Trustees, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, promotion, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, miscellaneous, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, publicity, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, mimeographed copies of excerpts from comments and lists to whom mimeographed material was sent, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, postcard survey, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, general, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, publicity, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, Mortimer Adler, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, budget, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, William Cornish, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, general, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, A. M. Gilbert, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, C. F. Hansen, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, William B. Harrell, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, William McGuinneas, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, publicity, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, sale of, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, Victor Van Der Linde, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, Mortimer Adler, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure Sherman Dryer, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, John P. Howe, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, transcript, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, insurance, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, mail report, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, Dale O'Brien, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, Mrs. William O'Meara, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, Revere Copper & Brass (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, St. Georges & Keyes, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, St. Georges, Maubert, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, Station WGN, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, Victor Van Der Linde, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Broadcasting, Human Adventure, general, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Broadcasting, Humble, Marion, 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Broadcasting, Humble, Marion, 1942-1943 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Broadcasting, Hutchins-Adler show, 1942-1943 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Broadcasting, Ingham, Travis, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Broadcasting, Institute of Radio Policy, draft by Mr. Howe for possible submission to Mr. Noble, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Broadcasting, Janeway, Eliott, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Broadcasting, Johnson, Kay, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Broadcasting, Johnson, Kay, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Broadcasting, Johnson, Laura, 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Broadcasting, Johnson, Laura, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Broadcasting, LaRoche, Chester, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Broadcasting, Lewis, William B., 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Broadcasting, Lewis, William B., 1940-1941 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Broadcasting, Lewis, William B., 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Broadcasting, Lewis, Captain Raymond C. New Tools for Learning, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Broadcasting, Lohr, Major Lenox, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Broadcasting, MacFarlane, W.B., 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Broadcasting, Miller, Allen, 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Broadcasting, Mutual Broadcasting System, 1942-1943, McClintock, Miller Schreiber, F. P. (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Broadcasting, Mutual Broadcasting System, 1943-1944 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Broadcasting, Mutual Broadcasting System, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Broadcasting, National Broadcasting Company, 1937-1938, Dyke, Kenneth Lohr, Lenox Lovell, Maurice Royal, John Sarnoff, David Tramell, Niles Waller, Judith (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Broadcasting, National Broadcasting Company, 1939-1940, Dyke, Kenneth Mason, Frank E. Morgan, Clay Royal, John F. Russell, Frank Strotz, Sidney M. Waller, Judith (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Broadcasting, National Broadcasting Company, 1940-1941, Artists Service Bronson, Ed Carling, Phillips Dyke, Ken Kobak, Edward Kopf, Harry G. Malone, Ted Menser, C. L. Morton, Alfred H. Mullen, Frank Royal, John Smith, Bernie Strotz, Sidney Waller, Judith Witmer, Roy (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Broadcasting, National Broadcasting Company, 1941-1942, Kopf, Harry Mullen, Frank Preston, Walter G. Royal, John Russell, Frank Strotz, Sidney Thrower, F. M., Jr. Waller, Judith (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Broadcasting, National Broadcasting Company, 1942-1943, Fisher, Sterling Jordan, Max Kopf, Harry Miller, Burke Mullen, Frank Paulus, Burton Royal, John Waller, Judith Witmer, Roy (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Broadcasting, National Broadcasting Company, 1943-1944 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Broadcasting, National Broadcasting Company, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Broadcasting, New Tools for Learning, 1943-1944 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Broadcasting, New Tools for Learning, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Broadcasting, Newton, Charles, 1937-1938 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Broadcasting, Nielsen, A. C. Company, survey of Round Table and Human Adventure, 1939-1940 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Broadcasting, Paley, William, 1939-1940 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Broadcasting, Paley, William, 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Broadcasting, Paley, William, 1941-1942 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Broadcasting, Paley, William, 1942-1943 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Broadcasting, Perry, Lucy, 1937-1938 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Broadcasting, Perry, Lucy, 1939-1940 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Broadcasting, Perry, Lucy, 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Broadcasting, Perry, Lucy, 1941-1942 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Broadcasting, Perry, Lucy, 1942-1943 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Broadcasting, Philco, 1940-1941, Ballantine, John Loveman, E. B. Ramsdell, Sayre (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Broadcasting, Philco, 1941-1942, Ballantyne, John Loveman, E. B. Ramsdell, Sayre Fizdale, Tom (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Broadcasting, Preston, Walter, 1939-1940 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Broadcasting, Preston, Walter, 1940-1941 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Broadcasting, Probst, George, 1941-1942 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Broadcasting, Probst, George, 1942-1943 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Broadcasting, Probst, George, 1943-1944 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Broadcasting, Probst, George, 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Broadcasting, Radio Broadcasting, chapter from William Benton's book on the University of Chicago's public relations, 1937-1938 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Broadcasting, Radio Committee, including outline of "Radio Broadcasting: A Challenge to the Educator", 1937-1938 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Broadcasting, Radio Committee, 1941-1942 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Broadcasting, Radio Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Broadcasting, Radio Committee, 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Broadcasting, Radio Office Budget, 1943-1944 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Broadcasting, Radio Office Budget, 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Broadcasting, Revere, Tom, 1939-1940 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Broadcasting, Reynolds, Stanley, 1941-1942 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Broadcasting, Reynolds, Stanley, 1942-1943 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Broadcasting, Robertson, Ruth, 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Broadcasting, Robson, William, 1939-1940 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Broadcasting, Rosell, Anne, 1943-1944 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, 1937-1938 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, analysis of subject matter, 1937-1938 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, announcements, 1937-1938 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, comments, 1937-1938 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, memorandum on budget, 1937-1938 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, miscellaneous correspondence, including Drew Pearson – Herbert Hoover incident, 1939-1940 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, general, 1940-1941 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Look story, 1940-1941 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, general, 1941-1942, Letters from listeners Scott, Albert Yale University Press (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Life story, 1941-1942 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, memorandum, 1941-1942 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, budget, 1942-1943 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, general, 1942-1943 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, general, 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, personnel, 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, script, 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, statistics, 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, survey, Howe comments on, 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Hudson, 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Lasswell, 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Logan, 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, general, 1944-1945 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Cooperative Analysis of Broadcasting, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Gordon Dupee, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Virginia Hawk, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Hooper Rating, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Kay Johnson, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Liberty Magazine, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, National Broadcasting Company, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, participants invitations, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, George Probst, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Niles Trammell, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Judith Waller, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, general, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Sloan Foundation, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Alfred Sloan, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Harold Sloan, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, R. E. Lewis, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Broadcasting, Round Table, Arnold Zurcher, 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Broadcasting, Sandburg, Carl, 1939-1940 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Broadcasting, Scammon, Richard, 1939-1940 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Broadcasting, Scammon, Richard, 1940-1941 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Broadcasting, Scammon, Richard, 1941-1942 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Broadcasting, "Scammon incident", 1941-1942 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Broadcasting, Siepmann, C. A., 1940-1941 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Broadcasting, Siepmann, C. A., 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Broadcasting, Siepmann, C. A., 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Broadcasting, Sloan Foundation, October – December 1938, 1937-1938 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Broadcasting, Sloan Foundation, January – June 1938, 1937-1938 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Broadcasting, Sloan Foundation, 1939-1940 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Broadcasting, Sloan Foundation, 1940-1941 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Broadcasting, Sloan Foundation, 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Broadcasting, Sloan Foundation, 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Broadcasting, Sloan Foundation, 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Broadcasting, Sloan Foundation, budget, 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Broadcasting, Sloan Foundation, 1944-1945 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Broadcasting, Spencer, Dean William, 1937-1938 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Broadcasting, Studio site, proposed, blueprints, 1937-1938 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Broadcasting, Sub-committee on Radio, 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Broadcasting, Thomas Norman, 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Broadcasting, Trammell, Niles, 1939-1940 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Broadcasting, Trammell, Niles, 1940-1941 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Broadcasting, Trammell, Niles, 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Broadcasting, Trammell, Niles, 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Broadcasting, Trammell, Niles, 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Broadcasting, Trammell, Niles, 1944-1945 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Broadcasting, University Broadcasting Council, 1937-1938 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Broadcasting, University Broadcasting Council, 1939-1940 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Broadcasting, Waller, Judith, 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Broadcasting, Waller, Judith, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Broadcasting, Weckler, Joseph, 1937-1938 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Broadcasting, Whitman, Alfred R. 1940-1941 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Broadcasting, Whitman, Alfred R. 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Brown, Dan, 1939-1940 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Brown, Lewis, 1941-1942 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Bruening, Chancellor, "Colleges and Public Life", 1937-1938 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Budget, 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Budget, 1945-1946 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Burden, William Douglas, 1940-1941 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Burke, Julia, 1937-1938 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Burns, Robert K., 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Bursar's Office, 1941-1942 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Bursar's Office, 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Bursar's Office, 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Bursar's Office, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Business Problems Bureau, 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Business Problems Bureau, 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Bye, George T., 1937-1938 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Bye, George T., 1939-1940 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Bye, George T., 1940-1941 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Bye, George T., 1941-1942 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Bye, George T., 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Bye, George T., 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Bye, George T., 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- C, general, 1937-1938, Cahill, Mrs. J. M. Campus Newsreel Caplan, Sidney Carlson, A. J. Carter, Irene Catlin, Randolph Cavenay, William T. Central Hanover Bank and Trust Company (Box 18, Folder 1)
- C, general, 1937-1938, Chamberlain, John Chaos Club Chicago Club Chicago Tribune Clark, Charles E. (Box 18, Folder 2)
- C, general, 1937-1938, Cohn, Marcus Collen, Mae Compton, A. H. Compton, Don Compton, Richard Comptroller, report of, 1937-1938 Conant, James Condon, Ralph Connell, Edward Copeland, Senator Royal S. Corey, Stephen M. Cox, Leilyn M. Crane, R. S. Cresap, Mark Cushman, Robert E. (Box 18, Folder 3)
- C, general, 1938-1939, Cap and Gown Carlson, A. J. Carlson, Robert Carlson, Mrs. Robert Central Hanover Bank and Trust Company Cinema Progress (Box 18, Folder 4)
- C, general, 1938-1939, Chase, Chancellor H. W. Chester, C. M. Chicago Association of Commerce Chicago Schools Chicago Daily News Chicago Tribune Christian German Refugees Committee Citizens Schools Committee Citizenship and Naturalization Committee City Club of Chicago Clifford, John (Box 18, Folder 5)
- C, general, 1938-1939, Cole, Fay Cooper Collen, Mae Compton, A. H. Comptroller Consolidated Book Publishing Company Continental Illinois National Bank and Trust Company (Box 18, Folder 6)
- C, general, 1939-1940, Cameron, D. F. Cap and Gown Carlson, Robert Carlson, Mrs. Robert Carnegie Foundation Case, Leland (Box 18, Folder 7)
- C, general, 1939-1940, Chalfonte-Haddon, Hall Chapman, John Chicago Association of Commerce "Chicago List," October 10, 1939 Chicago Ethical Society Chicago Times Chicago Tribune Children's Bureau Ciccarelli, A. Clark, Herman Clement, A. M. Cleveland Plain Dealer, Robert F. Stephan (Box 18, Folder 8)
- C, general, 1939-1940, Colgate University College Years Columbia Pictures Corporation Colwell, Ernest C. Compton, Arthur H. Congress on Education for Democracy Consolidate Book Publishers, Inc., L. Davidow Continental Banking Company Corner, Charles B. Courier Creamery Package Manufacturing Company Creese, James Cromwell, James H. R. Crowell, Thomas Company Crowell-Collier Publishing Company Crowery, George D. Cunningham, John P. Czeisler, Mrs. A. (Box 18, Folder 9)
- C, general, 1940-1941, Cap and Gown Capes, R. W. R. Carlson, Robert Carr, Charlotte Carter, John Franklin Case, Norman Cate, James Cates, V. Virgina Cattell, J. McKeen Chamberlin, John Chapman, John Chase, Stuart Chicago Daily News Chicago Herald American Chicago Teachers Union Child Interests Clemenko, H. B., Look Cleveland College Cleveland Plain Dealer Clough, DeWitt (Box 18, Folder 10)
- C, general, 1940-1941, Cohen, L. Lewis Cole, Fay Cooper Colgate University Collen, Mae Collette, Maurice Colwell, E. C. Columbia Lecture Bureau Columbia University Committee for Inter-American Cooperation Committee for a National Science Fund Common Ground Compere, Edward L. Conant, James Congresso Inter-Americano Conradt, L. R. Cooke, Dwight Country Home for Convalescent Children Cowan, Louis Crane, A. G. Crane, Mrs. Richard T. Craven, T. A. M. Crerar Library Croft, J. F. Cross, T. P. Crowell-Collier Publishing Company Curtis Publishing Company (Box 18, Folder 11)
- C, general, 1941-1942, Order of "C" Caldwell, O. H. Calendar, Weekly Calvin, L. S. Cameron, Mr. Canada Dry Cantril, Hadley Cantu, Carlos Carlson, Frank Carlson, Robert Carney, T. J. Carpenter, Mrs. John Alden Carr, Charlotte Carter, Marian S. Carter, Wesley Catchings, Waddill Cazalet, Victor Chapel, Rockefeller Memorial Chapman, John William Charan, David Chase, George S. Chenery, William L. Cherne, Leo Chicago Herald-American Chicago Historical Society Chicago and Western Indiana Railroad Co. Chicago Medical Society Chicago Surface Lines Chicago Technological College Clark, Dorothy Clark, John Clark, Walter Classical Outlook Claypool, E. W. Clayton, Will (Box 18, Folder 12)
- C, general, 1940-1941, Colby, Charles C. Coleman, John Collen, Mae Columbia Lecture Bureau Colwell, E. C. Committee on Development Common Ground Compere, Dr. E. L. Consolidated Clipping Service Conway, Carl Cooper, Sherman Cooper, Thomas P. Coordination of Information Cosmopolitan Cornell University Costello, Mrs. Helen Coward, Thomas R. Cowles, Gardner Cowles, John Cowling, Donald J. Cox, Garfield Craig, Ellen Crain, G. E. Crane, A. G. Craven, Avery O. Crawford, Alfred R. Creel, Herlee Cressingham, Mrs. R. H. Croneis, Carey Cultural and Commercial Committee Culver, Sydney Cummings, Major J. M. Cunningham, James D. Cutter, Mrs. Charles F. (Box 18, Folder 13)
- C, general, 1942-1943, Cannon, Paul R. Carlson, Robert B. Carnahan, C. C. Carnovsky, Leon Cayton, Horace R. Chalmers, Gordon Keith Chase, Harry Woodburn Chase, Stuart Clark, Dean A. Clark, Walter W. (Box 18, Folder 14)
- C, general, 1942-1943, Coelln, Ott Colby, Charles C. Collegiate Bureau Collen, Mae Colwell, E. C. Commonwealth Edison Company Cooper, Mary-Co Cowles Commission Cox, Garfield Craven, Avery Croneis, Carey Cromwell, Thomas I., Jr. Culbertson Cusack, James (Box 18, Folder 15)